Johnathan Alderson

Cape Town, South Africa Contact: 079 112 6539

Email: aldersonj012@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

I am an ambitious, hardworking individual who thrives on connecting with people and overcoming challenges. As a strong leader, I motivate others, and I am committed to pushing my limits to achieve success. Despite my limited work experience, I believe my eagerness to learn, combined with my dedication and work ethic, will enable me to achieve great success.

PERSONAL DETAILS

• RSA ID # - 010315 5112 081

Driver's License – Code 08Status – Single

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

2019 - Grade 12 National Senior Certificate (meets the minimum requirements for a

Bachelor's degree, Diploma or Higher Certificate study)

Studied: Afrikaans

English

Mathematics Literacy

Business Studies

Tourism

Computer Application Technology

WORK EXPERIENCE

2019 - DECEMBER - MARCH 2020 - KOOPMANSKRAAL FARM ESTATE

Farm assistant

- Assisted in managing and caring for a flock of sheep, insuring their health and well-being
- Contributed to vineyard maintenance.
- Gained hands on experience in animal care and agricultural practices, developing strong organizational and problem-solving skills.

2020 - FEBRUARY - APRIL, FEBRUARY 2022 - APRIL 2022- WELLINGTON WINES

Wine-maker assistant

- Assisted in various stages of winemaking, including managing machinery, fermentation, and aging process.
- Monitored and maintained fermentation temperature and equipment to ensure optimal wine quality.
- Gained knowledge in the science and techniques behind winemaking, such as monitoring acidity, and maintaining hygiene standards.
- Developed skills in attention to detail, teamwork, and problem-solving, as well as a strong understanding of the production process.

MAY 2022 - AUGUST 2022 - SIZZLERS

Assistant Manager

- Ensured stock availability and assisted in inventory management to maintain smooth operations.
- Helped staff with cleaning, ensuring the establishment maintained high hygiene standards.
- Managed and supervised staff, ensuring effective teamwork and a positive work environment.
- Developed leadership and organization skills by overseeing daily operations and maintaining customer satisfaction.

NOVEMBER 2022 - FEBRUARY 2024 - VIETNAM

English Teacher

- Taught English to students ranging from kindergarten to 30 years old, adopting lessons to different learning levels.
- Managed classroom behavior and developed problem-solving strategies for difficult students.
- Created engaging lesson plans and interactive activities to enhance language learning.
- Gained strong leadership, adoptability, and conflict resolution skills.

INTERESTS

- 1. Sports –Golf, Team Sports
- 2. Socializing with people
- 3. Reading personal development books

REFERENCE

Christof Briers-Louw - Contact number: 082 493 9932

Daniel Slabber - Contact number: 084 515 1071

Tuan Pham - +84 274 3946789